{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208072242","data":{"timestamp":" 947208072242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" 608d17b9-ba1c-41a1-aab0-775f0733ec74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208092889","data":{"timestamp":" 947208092889"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208095038","data":{"timestamp":" 947208095037"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208097158","data":{"timestamp":" 947208097157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208100342","data":{"timestamp":" 947208100341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208102606","data":{"timestamp":" 947208102605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208104873","data":{"timestamp":" 947208104872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208107763","data":{"timestamp":" 947208107763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208109937","data":{"timestamp":" 947208109936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208112174","data":{"timestamp":" 947208112173"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208115436","data":{"timestamp":" 947208115435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208117523","data":{"timestamp":" 947208117522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208119625","data":{"timestamp":" 947208119625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208122529","data":{"timestamp":" 947208122528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208124713","data":{"timestamp":" 947208124713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208126907","data":{"timestamp":" 947208126907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208129901","data":{"timestamp":" 947208129901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208132237","data":{"timestamp":" 947208132237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208134616","data":{"timestamp":" 947208134615"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208137659","data":{"timestamp":" 947208137659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208139777","data":{"timestamp":" 947208139777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208141910","data":{"timestamp":" 947208141910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208145078","data":{"timestamp":" 947208145078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208147286","data":{"timestamp":" 947208147285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208149460","data":{"timestamp":" 947208149459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208152623","data":{"timestamp":" 947208152622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208155066","data":{"timestamp":" 947208155065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208157502","data":{"timestamp":" 947208157501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208160671","data":{"timestamp":" 947208160670"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208162959","data":{"timestamp":" 947208162958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208165226","data":{"timestamp":" 947208165225"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208168241","data":{"timestamp":" 947208168241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208170442","data":{"timestamp":" 947208170442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208172586","data":{"timestamp":" 947208172586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208175450","data":{"timestamp":" 947208175449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208177812","data":{"timestamp":" 947208177811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208180188","data":{"timestamp":" 947208180187"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208183374","data":{"timestamp":" 947208183373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208185770","data":{"timestamp":" 947208185769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208188187","data":{"timestamp":" 947208188186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208191182","data":{"timestamp":" 947208191182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208193483","data":{"timestamp":" 947208193482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208195771","data":{"timestamp":" 947208195770"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208199028","data":{"timestamp":" 947208199028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208201309","data":{"timestamp":" 947208201309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208203582","data":{"timestamp":" 947208203581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208206963","data":{"timestamp":" 947208206962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208209435","data":{"timestamp":" 947208209434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208211903","data":{"timestamp":" 947208211902"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208214787","data":{"timestamp":" 947208214787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208217006","data":{"timestamp":" 947208217005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208219208","data":{"timestamp":" 947208219207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208222654","data":{"timestamp":" 947208222653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208224998","data":{"timestamp":" 947208224997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208227368","data":{"timestamp":" 947208227368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208230473","data":{"timestamp":" 947208230472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208232766","data":{"timestamp":" 947208232765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208235023","data":{"timestamp":" 947208235022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208238060","data":{"timestamp":" 947208238059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208240202","data":{"timestamp":" 947208240201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208242365","data":{"timestamp":" 947208242364"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208245541","data":{"timestamp":" 947208245540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208247793","data":{"timestamp":" 947208247792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208250050","data":{"timestamp":" 947208250049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208253289","data":{"timestamp":" 947208253288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208255547","data":{"timestamp":" 947208255546"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208257778","data":{"timestamp":" 947208257777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208261019","data":{"timestamp":" 947208261018"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208263380","data":{"timestamp":" 947208263380"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208265733","data":{"timestamp":" 947208265732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208268913","data":{"timestamp":" 947208268912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208271259","data":{"timestamp":" 947208271259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208271324","data":{"timestamp":" 947208271323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947208271412","data":{"timestamp":" 947208271412"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000107_042049"," gameId":" b49b21e5-1dd1-4cff-8ab1-a57aa1a9ed45"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_37"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}